etrafficboss.com 2014-06-25

# Your Privacy | etrafficboss

THE COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

etrafficboss.com collects personally identifiable information when required to facilitate a business transaction involving one or more of our products or services, when supplied as an inquiry to such products or services, or when required for employment purposes. Of which, only the personally identifiable information that you voluntarily provide will be collected. In some instances, etrafficboss.com may collect personally identifiable information from a third party or entity that has your permission to share your personal information. etrafficboss.com reserves the right to refuse to provide such products or services should the product or service depend on personally identifiable information in which you are unwilling to provide. Personally identifiable information can be defined as your name, shipping and/or mailing address, project street address, telephone number, email address, and\or credit or debit card account numbers.

ORDER FULFILLMENT PRACTICES

When ordering products or services via etrafficboss.com you may be asked to provide pertinent financial information, such as your credit card number, expiration date, money order, wire transfer or check information, in addition to your contact information. This information is used for billing purposes and may be stored for recursive processing for services that are billed on a reoccurring basis. To initiate the billing process we must share your personal and financial information with the merchant bank for authorization and approval. Should any attempt to bill you fail, we will then in turn use your supplied contact information to contact you for resolution.

THE SHARING OF YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

Under no circumstances does etrafficboss.com sell or lease any of your personally identifiable information, either in whole or in part. However, it is sometimes necessary to provide your personally identifiable information to third parties with whom we conduct business with in order to provide you various products or services that you have specifically requested. From time to time we may also provide portions of your personally identifiable information to third party businesses for analytical purposes to improve upon the products or services we provide. The portions thereof usually consist of your customer ID number, an email address, the city, state and a ZIP code. Only under these conditions will we share your personally identifiable information and when doing so, we take every measure to insure that the information is provided securely and without conflict of interest. Although etrafficboss.com will not be held responsible for any misuse of your information by any of the third parties with whom we conduct business with, we do assure you that we only conduct business with third parties that are legitimate businesses whom maintain and practice a privacy policy that is of equivalent or higher standards than the privacy policy herein.

COOKIES FROM etrafficboss.com 

Various portions of etrafficboss.com utilize cookies. Cookies are client-side text files that store bits of information about a visitor. This information can range from personal preferences to login session data. Cookies can only be read by the same web server that originally authored the cookie. etrafficboss.com utilizes cookies for tracking purchases, visitor navigation, authentication, and for analytical purposes. If your web browser is not cookie enabled then you may not be able to fully benefit from our products or services, as some of which are dependent on cookies. etrafficboss.com reserves the right to refuse to provide any products or services that are dependent on cookies to visitors who use a web browser that does not permit cookies.

OUR SECURTY PRACTICES

etrafficboss.com goes to great lengths to ensure that your personally identifiable information is secure. Our servers, which house your information, are stored in a secure facility consisting of multiple security cameras, alarms, 24X7 monitoring, and are only accessible to authorized personnel. We only authorize etrafficboss.com employee’s and\or people working on our behalf and under confidentiality agreements to access your information. Your information is only accessed when necessary and only under certain procedural safeguards. Whenever etrafficboss.com collects personally identifiable information from you, including but not limited to your credit card information, your information is submitted from your web browser to our servers via secured socket layer. Secured socket layer, also known as SSL, is a 128-bit encryption technology that is used by most major financial institutions to secure your sensitive financial data.

HOW WE USE LOG FILES

We use analytical software to track IP address information. This information is stored in log files and then analyzed to determine trends, visitor navigation, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are numerical ID’s appointed to machines upon establishing a network session, such as when connecting to the Internet. IP addresses can be traced to any one particular machine and can be associated with personally identifiable information through your Internet service provider. For security reasons, we link IP addresses to personally identifiable information and we do not distribute or share IP information with any third parties.

OUR POLICIES REGARDING CHILDREN

etrafficboss.com does not sell products for purchase by children. If you are under 18 years of age, please do not submit any information without the express consent and participation of a parent or guardian. We will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information via the Internet from children under the age of 18. etrafficboss.com is committed to protecting the welfare and privacy of children.

LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Throughout etrafficboss.com you may find links to other websites. etrafficboss.com will not be held responsible for the privacy practices of these websites. We encourage our visitors, and clients alike, to take caution when visiting such links and to always review the privacy policy practices of those websites before providing any personally identifiable information.

MANAGING YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

We enable our clients to manage their personally identifiable information via the account management area. This feature is pre-integrated and gives our clients the freedom to make any updates to their information, including their billing information, as necessary. Visitors whom have supplied us with personally identifiable information as an initial inquiry about our products or services, either via our web design quote system, Email, phone, or through any other medium cannot update their personally identifiable information via any control panel or any other mechanism.
